Watching this film on a large screen will take you to another world
I Am So Unique
I am so unique, known to all universe
I am so unique, no equals, no parallels!
I am frequented to inspire hope
With Allah’s mercy, for those who lose hope
I am so unique, known to all universe
I am so unique, no equals, no parallels!
I am frequented to inspire hope
With Allah’s mercy, for those who lose hope
I am still the Qiblah of those who seek Allah’s guidance
In my sanctuary, no worry, no fear
I am still a relic for people
Uniting worship, aspirations, and paths
I have great signs from Allah
No other sanctuary attained or ever had
Where else a ruby Stone could be found
Descending from the Paradise of the Most Merciful?
Whoever kisses it will be pardoned
No wonder the space is so crowded
Where else you find the Yamani corner?
To touch it is to be relived from sins and sorrows
And the enclosure of Ishmael
A prayer in it is like a prayer in me
And the Station of Abraham
Where he built and Muhammad prayed
Where else could you find Multazam?
Where supplications are made and accepted
My land is all blessed, all sanctuary
With joy for a resident and security for a visitor
In me is what pleases the repentant
And doubles the reward for good doers
I am so unique, no equals, no parallels!